

# Arantxa Astudillo

## **DIGITAL ARTIST**

arantxastudio.com

(650)279-7194

aaastudillo11@gmail.com

### **SUMMARY**

Dynamic and motivated visual artist with over two years of experience in digital mediums such as: 3D modeling and lighting, videography and post-editing, motion graphics, graphic design, and web design. Excellent team leader, collaborator, demonstrating strong communication and organization skills. Able to execute projects from concept to completion.

### **EDUCATION**

**Digital Media Art** - BFA - San Jose State University, San Jose, CA 2019 **Child Development** - AA - Foothill College, Los Altos, CA 2016

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Freelance Graphic Designer, Videographer/Post-Editor, Photographer Silicon Valley, CA 2020 - Current

- Designed logos for 3 separate Bay Area businesses: Berylus LLC, Elysium Hair Salon, and Jenergy Performance, to be used for websites, emails, and social media content.
- Photographed Jenergy Performance to be featured in Voyage LA Magazine.

# **Domestic Assistant & Tutor**, Los Altos, CA 2016 - 2020

- Designed and coached unique educational approaches that proved successful.
- Coordinated schedules with parental collaboration, reducing stress and increasing members' productivity.

# **Art Instructor**, The Creative Learning Loft, Redwood City, CA 2012 - 2016

- Applied art therapy principles to develop and lead art projects for over 60 students aged 5-10, based on the proper use of color theory, pencil, charcoal, acrylic paints, clay art and other art mediums.
- Exceeded parental expectations by improving children's mood, calming the body and mind, and amplifying the advantages of a project oriented mindset; which translated into student's educational workflow.

## **SKILLS**

# **Prototyping Software**

Sketch
Adobe Illustrator
Blender
Arduino
Processing
Fusion360

• Adobe Photoshop

# **Programming/Scripting Languages**

• JAVA • C++ • C# • HTML/CSS

## **Videography Tools**

DSLR
GoPro
Drone
Adobe Premiere Pro
Adobe After Effects
Audio Equipment

# Machinery/Crafting

• CNC Carver • Solder iron • 3D Printer • Laser Cutter

## **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

Osher CCC Transfer Student Scholarship - San Jose State University 2017

# Makers Faire, San Mateo, CA 2019

- Showcased in the global fair of innovative and self made technology.
- Built and programmed an interactive robot using Arduino, time to distance sensor, servos
- View at https://vimeo.com/375579474.